const decks = [
  {
    category: "Math",
    id: 0,
    cards: [
      { question: "Pytanie 1?", cardId: 92211, answer: "Odpowiedź 1" },
      { question: "Pytanie 2?", cardId: 31899, answer: "Odpowiedź 2" },
      { question: "Pytanie 3?", cardId: 37573, answer: "Odpowiedź 3" },
      { question: "Pytanie 4?", cardId: 38583, answer: "Odpowiedź 4" },
      { question: "Pytanie 5?", cardId: 16853, answer: "Odpowiedź 5" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
  {
    category: "English",
    id: 1,
    cards: [
      { question: "What is 2+2?", cardId: 97190, answer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 20/2?", cardId: 35106, answer: "10" },
      { question: "What is 2*18?", cardId: 60015, answer: "36" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
  {
    category: "Polish",
    id: 2,
    cards: [
      { question: "What is 2+2?", cardId: 66769, answer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 20/2?", cardId: 40723, answer: "10" },
      { question: "What is 2*18?", cardId: 47773, answer: "36" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
  {
    category: "Spanish",
    id: 3,
    cards: [
      { question: "What is 2+2?", cardId: 2560, answer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 20/2?", cardId: 43653, answer: "10" },
      { question: "What is 2*18?", cardId: 40805, answer: "36" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
  {
    category: "Biology",
    id: 4,
    cards: [
      { question: "What is 2+2?", cardId: 67929, answer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 20/2?", cardId: 68434, answer: "10" },
      { question: "What is 2*18?", cardId: 62244, answer: "36" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
  {
    category: "Chemistry",
    id: 5,
    cards: [
      { question: "What is 2+2?", cardId: 53959, answer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 20/2?", cardId: 2275, answer: "10" },
      { question: "What is 2*18?", cardId: 50383, answer: "36" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
  {
    category: "Art",
    id: 6,
    cards: [
      { question: "What is 2+2?", cardId: 94766, answer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 20/2?", cardId: 88642, answer: "10" },
      { question: "What is 2*18?", cardId: 34121, answer: "36" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
  {
    category: "French",
    id: 7,
    cards: [
      { question: "What is 2+2?", cardId: 88006, answer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 20/2?", cardId: 88118, answer: "10" },
      { question: "What is 2*18?", cardId: 31511, answer: "36" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
  {
    category: "Geography",
    id: 8,
    cards: [
      { question: "What is 2+2?", cardId: 55782, answer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 20/2?", cardId: 68068, answer: "10" },
      { question: "What is 2*18?", cardId: 70301, answer: "36" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
  {
    category: "History",
    id: 9,
    cards: [
      { question: "What is 2+2?", cardId: 81583, answer: "4" },
      { question: "What is 20/2?", cardId: 67905, answer: "10" },
      { question: "What is 2*18?", cardId: 87946, answer: "36" },
    ],
    infoData: {
      timesPlayed: 0,
      correctAnswers: 0,
      wrongAnswers: 0,
      lastPlayed: "22.10.2020",
    },
  },
];

export default decks;
